<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.loanshackprepaid.com"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
 <title>loanshackprepaid.com - Loans</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/taxonomy/loans</link>
 <description>loans
</description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>A Simple Guide before Acquiring a Holiday Loan</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/simple-guide-acquiring-holiday-loan</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Simple Guide before Acquiring a Holiday Loan&lt;br /&gt; We are all very excited as the holiday season is nearing.  However, many feel anxious spending for presents, party, a new home project, or even for a holiday vacation especially when the budget is tight during this time of season. Not wanting to spoil the joyfulness of the holidays because of lack of funds, holiday loans are being offered here and there by a lot of companies. Before you can be drawn quickly in getting one, here are three simple things you have to remember:&lt;br /&gt; First, think of your holiday goals in terms of your personal and familys needs. Jot down what you really want to have or do during the holidays. If you plan to have a vacation break with your family or be alone if youre single, make sure you have a clear plan where to go and how much you would want to spend for it, or research on places you want to go to set a clear budget. But if this coming holiday season, you wish to have something to buy or something to organize within your homes, then still list down the items and how much each item cost. Visit places where you can find shops that offer pre- holiday sale or special holiday coupons. Knowing your wishes or goals for the Christmas season will help you make a decision if you need to grab a holiday loan for that matter.&lt;br /&gt; Second, assess your current financial status. One question you can ask yourself is, &quot;Would I be able to give the monthly pay-off if I acquire a holiday loan?&quot; It is very important that you could do a simple addition and subtraction of your monthly income. Is it visible to you and viable on your finances that you can live after the holidays with another additional outlay? Undoubtedly, the status of your finances should be clear so that you can decide suitably if you will acquire a holiday loan.&lt;br /&gt; Lastly, do a research on companies offering holiday loans (even when you are still contemplating on getting one). In order to have a better insight if a loan for the holidays is a good step for you, give yourself time to research on the different offers by the different companies. Get the disadvantages and advantages to enable you have better options or best deals when you decide to have a go with it. It is good that you personally visit the business office of the company that offer such loans and spend time with their representatives so they can directly answer questions you have in mind. You can research on the internet to get a listing of companies offering holiday loans and check if they are within your area so you can pay a visit. Compare them based on the quality of service they provide, flexibility of loans, payment options, good feedback by customers, and a reputable market position.&lt;br /&gt; So before you really have to settle on a holiday loan, consider these things out and it might help you have a rewarding and a happier holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">170 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/simple-guide-acquiring-holiday-loan#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Things to Consider When Searching for Auto Loans</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/things-consider-when-searching-auto-loans</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Auto loans are part of purchasing a new or used vehicle when savings do not cover the amount on the vehicle. Finding an auto loan that fit personal needs requires a few considerations beforehand. When searching for the right loan, keeping some things in mind can narrow down the options and save time in the search. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Determine the Type of Loan: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Numerous types of auto loans are available to meet a wide range of needs. Depending on the type of vehicle and the lender, the auto loan that is best for individual needs will vary. Before looking at any lenders, narrow down the type of loans that are best suited to the purchase. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The common types of auto loans include used car loans, new vehicle loans, classic car loans and business car loans. Men and women who have a poor credit rating might also consider a bad credit loan to work around the traditional lenders and obtain funding for the vehicle. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The auto loan types can make a difference in the amount of funding provided, the interest rate and the repayment plans the lender makes available. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Setting the Loan Amount: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Another consideration is the budget. Before going to buy a vehicle, it is vital to set a budget. Some auto loans have a calculator available to help determine the monthly payments with interest rates added to the basic charges and based on the length of the loan. This helps determine how much to take out in the loan and avoids accidentally buying a more expensive car than it is possible to repay. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The budget should factor the interest rate, any added fees and the length of the loan to determine the final monthly payment. Without these factors, the loan amount can end up higher than expected. When in doubt about the cost, lower the amount to make monthly payments more affordable. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Comparison Shopping: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; As with any purchase, it is important to compare lenders and their quotes to find the best rates and deals. Lenders often vary in the interest charges they put on a loan, so shopping around and asking for numerous quotes can help find a lender who works for personal needs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Keep in mind that different types of lenders are available and sometimes comparing among the different types of specialized lenders might help lower the interest rate. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Check the Credit Score: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Before going to see any lender, get a copy of the credit report and credit score. A credit score is a major factor in the quoted interest charges. If the report has a mistake, correct it before seeking a loan. The mistakes can result in lower credit scores or negative marks on credit history that result in higher interest. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Auto loans are a long term debt that often lasts around five years. This means that the selection of a lender can make the difference between paying higher charges than necessary or paying an appropriate amount for the loan. Buying a car is not a dream if proper care is taken to find the best loan to meet a personal budget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">169 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/things-consider-when-searching-auto-loans#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>A Quik Look  Business Loans Basics</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/quik-look-%C2%96-business-loans-basics</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One must be well familiar with all the aspects of Business Loans. All matters are based on certain basics. Business Loan being a financial matter are also based on certain basics and it is extremely important to learn in detail about these basic before you decide to go for a Business Loan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Business Loan is a necessity in every business and there are many types of loans available for businessmen to obtain as per there requirement. Every businessman plans to get some loan for his and one time or another, this may be to compensate or reinforce is own working capital in order to meet a requirement which may not be within the capacity of the capital in the account, or to establish a new business for which an additional capital is needed or to buy certain additional or new appliances/gadgets to meet the increase demand of the business, or for payment of wages to some additional employees till the income generated is able to meet the expenses, or for expansion of space an essential requirement to expand the business &amp;amp; there can be numerous other reasons too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The important point is that will a businessman get the loan sanctioned when he/she applies for it, or will it be sanctioned in time to meet the requirement, or the amount of business loan sanctioned is same as applied or less and will the fewer amounts be sufficient to meet the need. Our endeavour here is to guide the businessmen for obtaining loan so that the businessman is able to obtain the Business loan without any problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first step after you decides to go for Business Loan is to select the Lender from whom you will like to get the money. Sources available are internet, friends, other businessmen and financial companies; having selected one lender the second step is to complete the paper work. The necessary form can be obtained from Internet or the office of the Lender, better option is the company where you can also be briefed in person in detail and you are likely not to miss out any information required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember it is not necessary that you have to be a businessman to apply for Business Loan, you may be an employed person and want to start your business, you are very much eligible for a business loan, but you must have knowledge of the type of loan you should apply for. All businessmen applying for Business Loans must also have the knowledge of the types of loans available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are TWO types of Business loans. The Short Term Business Loans and the Long Term Business Loans:-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short Term Business Loans  The word &quot;Term&quot; here is not related to terms and conditions, here it indicates the time period of the loan. These loans are normally for a shorter duration of time, say 6 months to12 months, therefore the amount of loan is also of smaller denomination a maximum of $100,000. Apply for this type of loan if your requirement is to invest money to generate an additional income in speed so that the loan is paid back within the prescribed period. Short Term Business Loans are mostly needed and beneficial for seasonal businesses. Long Term Business Loans  Loans involving large amount of money and for longer period of time are called the Long term Business Loans. The time period can extend from a minimum of 7 years to a longer period. The time frame depends on the amount of loan. This type of loans is mostly meant for large businesses to meet the requirements of extensions or additional machinery/ vehicles or buying new enterprises etc. Business Loan may be of any type it should be utilized for the purpose it is obtained for. Obtaining or giving a business loan is a source of income for both the Lender and the Borrower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">168 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/quik-look-%C2%96-business-loans-basics#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Healthcare Expenses Increasing Faster than Personal Revenue</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/healthcare-expenses-increasing-faster-personal-revenue</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Commonwealth Fund, health insurance costs are rising faster than personal income in all 50 states. Deductibles and other out of pocket expenses continue to go up, while incomes are going down. The Commonwealth Fund&#039;s study discovered several reasons for the rise in health care costs over recent years. Among the findings, it was discovered that employers are charging their employees higher costs to participate in health care plans. In addition, deductibles have risen 98 percent since 2003. This means that most people will have to pay for their own healthcare costs out of pocket for a greater length of time before their coverage kicks in. in addition, total premiums that employees pay annually average $3,721.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; This news hits close to home for many Americans who are dealing with other economic problems already. With employment rates mostly stagnating, foreclosures going up, student loan debt reaching one trillion dollars, and incomes going down, it&#039;s not getting any easier for most Americans to stay financially solvent in these trying times. For many Americans, the rise in health care costs is beginning to make the very idea of survival economically prohibitive. .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Many Americans, on the other hand, are being forced to discover creative new ways to pay for their health care costs. For example, some individuals whose incomes are preventing them from getting covered may take out short term loans in order to meet rising medical costs. Many short term loans are available, each coming with its distinct set of pros and cons. Payday loans, for instance, are one of the most popular types of short term loan. However, for most Americans they&#039;re not a feasible option for paying medical costs since they are usually only for a small amount and come with a short repayment period. This may influence some to turn instead to collateral loans, which offer a more robust amount in exchange for some piece of the borrower&#039;s property. One type of collateral loan that&#039;s becoming increasingly popular is called a car title loan. Motorists may find these to be a better option than other short term loans since they typically charge lower interest and come with longer repayment periods. Consumers who are interested in more information about car title loans can access sites such as &lt;a href=&quot;http://tfciloan.com&quot;&gt;http://tfciloan.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://acartitleloan.com&quot;&gt;http://acartitleloan.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; While there may be more than one way to skin the cat of health care costs, one thing is certain. Americans are going to need to take all the financial help they can get as health care costs continue to make themselves out of reach. It&#039;s simply irresponsible to live without health insurance, even if you find that it takes a chunk out of your discretionary income. To pay for ever rising health care costs, Americans will just have to budget more wisely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">167 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/healthcare-expenses-increasing-faster-personal-revenue#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Five Fair Rules For US Debit Deal</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/five-fair-rules-us-debit-deal</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;US politicians have been locked into negotiations about reducing the countrys discrepancy, with the two sides unable to agree a tax and spending package as the possibility of a debt default becomes visible. So what are the fair rules in such a situation? The risk could not be higher. As the clock indicates and time rallys towards 2 August, the possibility of the US defaulting on its debt grows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; To steer clear of the government is running out of money on that day and the economic upheaval some forecasters have predicted could happen as a end result the US must raise its debt limit above its current $14.3trillian so it can borrow more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Frequently, raising the debt top limit is a regulation, although with some political pomposity. But this time, the Republicans, who control the House of Representatives, have been adamant that there should be spending cuts to address the ballooning deficit, in exchange for increasing the debt limit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; All eyes have been on the White House, where President Obama and senior Democrats and Republicans have been unable to find common ground during a week of discussions. There have been reports of walkouts from both sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; According to forecasters the fait rules are following&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Keeping a list of issues you are willing to negotiate, and ranked in order of importance, is a fundamental requirement .Having this list helps incalculably when you sense the talks moving towards deadlock.&lt;br /&gt; In planning your strategy, you carefully determine what and when youre going to communicate to your corresponding person, If you reveal your &quot;red lines&quot; what you wont shunt on is early, youre showing them .In the debt talks, Republicans have said from the outset that any deal that includes new tax revenue will not work.&lt;br /&gt; Both sides in Washington have been lay blame on knowingly growing the stakes in order to reinforce their hand , Obama by saying he cant guarantee social security cheques will be paid next month, and some Republicans who say they wont vote to raise the debt top limit under any conditions.&lt;br /&gt; Both sides in the debt talks are unfastened groupings of warring tribes, Therefore there is a dance between internal politics and external discussions. Obama has also felt the heat from liberals in his party for saying he will consider cutting benefits like Medicare, which is paid to the mature.&lt;br /&gt; Negotiation is always a momentum game and that requires action-forcing events, Like deadlines, things to keep the thing moving forward. Without accomplishment forcing events, people are faced with hard choices. The symmetry is to do nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">166 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/five-fair-rules-us-debit-deal#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Debt Consolidation for Renters or Homeowners with Poor credit or No Equity</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/debt-consolidation-renters-or-homeowners-poor-credit-or-no-equity</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Debt consolidation reduction Programs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Debt consolidation reduction programs will require your entire high interest debts which you owe and consolidate them into one payment per month, with a lower rate of interest. Your monthly payment for your one loan should also be a substantially lower payment for you monthly. The issue for many consumers with this loan plan&#039;s that they can have to have collateral just like a home or other good assets to acquire the loan. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With collateral you can obtain a lower payment per month, but missing a payment just isn&#039;t an option. Should you miss a payment, plus you&#039;ve got placed your property up as collateral, you take the chance of losing your home. Another problem with investing in this type of home loan is lots of people end up repeating their same bad habits and increases more credit card debt. This is their explanation hold the loan to settle, and new credit cards to cover. You have to be well disciplined with ourselves and not remove any more charge cards until your loan pays off entirely. If you can do that, a debt consolidation loan program having a lower interest may fit your situation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consumer credit counseling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bankruptcy is on the minds of many people since they dont know very well what else to complete. They ought to seek the help of the credit guidance service to check if they can repair their credit. Professional counseling can instruct you on your particular financial situation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you have established an association using a credit counselor you&#039;ll sit down and look at all of your income and debts. Your counselor will have to understand specifically what your credit card debt is, and the other debts your debt, so that you can set up an agenda which fits your life-style. All income getting into the house is going to be totaled up as well as your debts will probably be totaled to find out what usable income you might have to repay your creditors. Your counselor could probably speak to your creditors and acquire some of your financial troubles reduced or get you lower rates of interest on your debts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your counselor will set up a debt repayment plan and manage the master plan to suit your needs along with your creditors. You&#039;ll pay the counselor one monthly payment, as well as the counselor pays off your creditors. You will have payment plan you have to keep up with for 3 to 5 years, before your creditors are paid off in full. Professional credit counseling just isn&#039;t free each agency charges differently. Some possess a flat fee that you will pay while some use your first payments for their fees. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Debt settlement&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Debts settlements companies will tell you to avoid paying your credit card issuers and pay right into a fund monthly until you have enough to repay one of the creditors. A counselor doing work for the debt settlement company will get hold of your creditors and acquire lower settlement agreements for your benefit. You in turn will give the debt settlement company every month. Funds will build up until one of the creditors need what exactly is inside your fund like a full payment of the debt. Your counselor will pay that creditor and you may still pay in to the fund to work off the next creditor. Payments to those companies differ from one company to the next as well as their fees could possibly get costly. One trouble with this kind of situation would be that the creditors can still give you bills, and require to the court for your full amount. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">165 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/debt-consolidation-renters-or-homeowners-poor-credit-or-no-equity#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Merchant Cash Advance At You Service</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/merchant-cash-advance-you-service</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Small Business needs financial help, it is the Merchant Cash Advance which comes and provides necessary funding and that too in a record shortest possible time. This means Merchant Cash Advance (MCA) is always at your serviceSmall Businesses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The most popular of all the financial institutions lending money to businesses in financial troubles is the Merchant Cash Advance, the reason behind this popularity is the time MCA takes to sanction the loan, (that is less than 3 days) and the number of options it provides you to utilize the loan. It really comes to the rescue of Small Business in financial troubles. This helps the small businesses to prosper and improve their business activities in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; In the prevailing economic environments no businessmen can afford to tolerate the tough and strict restriction laid by the banks and some other financial institutions for obtaining loans. The banks are also known for taking long time,( over 90 days) to sanction the amounts, in most cases the amount sanctioned is far less than the amount demanded by the entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Merchant Cash Advance is a process based on future likely income of the borrower. The businessmen qualify for the loan based on two factors, firstly the financial bank statements of last few months and secondly the credit card history of the business. The credit score dictates the maximum amount that can be sanctioned, bad credit score has no bearing on the sanctioning of the loan. The pay back of the loan is based on the mutually agreed percentage of receivables (Through Master and Visa Credit Cards) of future sales/ income of the business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; This is an unimaginable facility for the businessmen. There is no tension of fixed monthly installments; there is no worry of any time period. More the income earned by the business in a particular month, higher the amount of installment, less the income less the payback. So the sale and the income decide when the loan will be paid back in full.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The payback can be also be worked out on daily basis, working on the same system. The businessmen are at ease and can concentrate free of worries on other important issues related to the business. The credit card Scratch Machines plays an important role in the process. The lender simply informs the credit card company the percentage of credit card sales to be transferred to him on daily or monthly basis, the amount is automatically remitted in the lenders account, a facility   that safeguards his cash given by the lender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The majority of businessmen who are enjoying the facilities of Merchant Cash Advance are the one who were denied the loan by the banks for not meeting their prerequisites laid down to qualify for the advance, such as bad credit history, type of business, not having a collateral to offer and other requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Merchant Cash Advance does not lay any such conditions or prerequisites on the loan seekers. In the contrary they tend to provide the required cash in as less time as possible provided the nominal paper work is complete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">164 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/merchant-cash-advance-you-service#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Business Loan that to Hassle Free</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/business-loan-hassle-free</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What about getting a business loan sanctioned and that to without any worries and hassles of getting struck up in lengthy procedures and paper works. Businessmen around the country must learn to prepare their case when applying for a Business Loan, short term or long term Business Loan. The best way to do so is to put yourself in the shoes of the bank or the leasing company manager, ask yourself a simple question. What all you would expect from a borrower who approaches you for a Business loan?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The most important information you would like to know is the ability of the borrower to return the loan and in what time frame. Is the borrower in a position to provide some sort of guarantee, like mortgaging some property, if so required. Now as a borrower make a detailed plan for the business loan and apply only when you have answered all such questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Your plan for the Business Loan should include the following information:-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     Proof of your ability to pay back the business loan in full. Show your bank statements and bank guarantees. Your balance in your account will be an ample proof of your ability to pay back. The money in the bank can be shown as a capital for use in a future investment.&lt;br /&gt;     A comprehensive future business plan will be able to convince that the Business Loan will be utilized in a manner that the business will be able to generate enough capital to payback the Business Loan in full and in time.&lt;br /&gt;     Regulation and control of your cash flow will also convince the loan manager to sanction your loan. This can be done as part of your future business plan, indicating as to how you intend to handle all your financial matters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Lay importance to these very simple requirements before you apply for your Business Loan and succeed in getting the capital essentially required for your future Business plan without any hassles and delays. Remember the loan manager is always willing to give business loan to businessmen who approach them, the only simple requirements are the one explained above. Leasing companies and banks are to lease money as part of their businesses, they also earn fair amount of capital from these transactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">163 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/business-loan-hassle-free#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Common Signs of Loan Modification Scams and How to Avoid Them</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/common-signs-loan-modification-scams-and-how-avoid-them</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those considering loan modification, times have likely been better. Generally, people only seek information on modifying their loans after having some difficulty keeping up with their mortgage payments and other bills. They see this as an option to stay in their homes and continue getting their finances back on track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Unfortunately, some loan modification companies are preying on these individuals with false promises and guarantees that are too good to be true. Since the Home Affordable Modification Program, or HAMP, began many opportunistic individuals, including some loan modification attorneys, have attempted to profit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Here are some warning signs that one of these loan modification companies is attempting to add you to their list of victims. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 1) They ask for upfront payments. This is one of the most important flags because of its predatory nature, and also because it is illegal to ask for money before their work on the modification has begun. Also, you should never make your monthly payments to the loan modification attorney or any other third party. Your loan is still serviced by the lender and that&#039;s where your payments should be sent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 2) They offer results that are too good. While the purpose of the program is to reduce your monthly payments to an affordable amount, either through spreading out the repayment period, reducing interest rates or reducing the principal, if the offer sounds exceptional then be wary. Any &quot;guarantee&quot; or &quot;promise&quot;, whether it is an end to foreclosure proceedings or even acceptance into the program, should be approached with caution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 3) They can&#039;t, or won&#039;t, explain the services they are going to do. While the loan modification process can sometimes seem difficult or tedious for homeowners, the process is relatively straightforward. Your lender supplies a packet that must be filled out, generally including an authorization to release tax information, proof of income and bank statements, as well as an explanation of why you are having difficulty making the payments. There is no mystery or secret to the process and any reputable loan modification company should be able to explain the process to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Loan modifications can be confusing to many people but guard yourself against potential scams by watching out for upfront payments, too-good-to-be-true results, and mysterious methods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">162 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/common-signs-loan-modification-scams-and-how-avoid-them#comments</comments>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Bad credit Business Loans &amp; Banks !!! Think Twice</title>
 <link>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/bad-credit-business-loans-banks-think-twice</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any business, either new or established may require additional capital and that too at very crucial times. The entrepreneur will be in a great hurry/urgency to obtain Business loan from any source available in the market. He/she is likely to get a blank chit from most of the banks and they are always not ready to lend money as Bad Credit Business Loan . This is the common practice, studied in different researches over cash flow and business loan domain; For any upcoming businessmen it is a real challenging situation, which creates a lot of worries and tensions, especially when the money is urgently require and it is not available on immediate basis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; In case, you have an established enterprise and you require Bad Credit Business Loan , the banks will still level high the costs of sanctioning, nearly up to 20-30%. They will ask for guarantees in shape of collateral before they provide you some money. Moreover the bank loans also require a heavy load of paper work. The time to get the amount sanctioned will remain at the discretion of the bank; your urgency for the cash will not play be in role as far as the bank is concerned. In most of the cases this cause a definite frustration at your end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Bad Credit Business Loan obtained from the banks are based on high interest rates and are paid back on fixed amount criteria. Beside the different business related concerns, these monthly fix amount to be paid back (each month or after an agreed period time) remains a headache and continuous worry for the entrepreneur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; It is a fact that when you ask for a Business Loan from any financial institution you will be paying back more than what you will pay back in case the Business Loan from the bank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Reports shows that the the request of urgent business load from a bank usually take longer then its urgency. In such short period the bank will still be processing your papers. The amount of Business Loan required by you will probably be sanctioned in full by the financial institutions, where as the bank will never sanction the applied amount in full.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; The major advantage you have when obtaining Bad Credit Business Loan from any good financial institution, it is involves a simple and quick procedure. Cash will be in your hands within a maximum period of 10 days; a facility one cannot imagine when dealing with a bank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-field-taxonomy field-type-taxonomy-term-reference field-label-above clearfix&quot;&gt;&lt;h3 class=&quot;field-label&quot;&gt;taxonomy: &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;links&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;taxonomy-term-reference-0&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/taxonomy/loans&quot; typeof=&quot;skos:Concept&quot; property=&quot;rdfs:label skos:prefLabel&quot; datatype=&quot;&quot;&gt;Loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 06:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">161 at http://www.loanshackprepaid.com</guid>
 <comments>http://www.loanshackprepaid.com/loans/bad-credit-business-loans-banks-think-twice#comments</comments>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>

<!-- Page cached by Boost @ 2013-12-09 13:09:11, expires @ 2013-12-09 14:09:11, lifetime 1 hour -->